Finding Aid for Jonathan W. Bulkley papers, 1973-1976
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Jonathan W. Bulkley papers 1973-1976
Bulkley, Jonathan W.
8586 Aa 2
Member of the Ann Arbor (Mich.) Housing Commission, president of the commission, 1974-1976. Working files, including records of meetings, policy statements, and staff materials documenting the work of the commission.
2 linear feet
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Jonathan W. Bulkley (donor no. 5969 ).
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Jonathan Bulkley was a member of the Ann Arbor Housing Commission (AAHC) from 1973 to 1976, and president of the commission from 1974 until 1976.
Throughout his tenure as the Housing Commissioner, Bulkley oversaw the operation of an extremely troubled agency. Intense factionalism afflicted the commission's staff, and severe problems arose regarding several of the public housing sites administered by the body.
The Bulkley papers consist of his working files, including records of meetings, policy statements, and staff materials documenting the work of the Ann Arbor Housing Commission. The papers have been divided into three series: Ann Arbor Housing Commission meeting files; Policy statements and other materials; and Organizational files.
Subjects:
Housing--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Ann Arbor (Mich.). Housing Commission.; Dwellings--Michigan--Ann Arbor.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Dwellings.; Dwellings--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Housing.; Miller Manor (Ann Arbor, Mich.)
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Ann Arbor Housing Commission meeting files
  - March 29, 1973 Special Meeting (Box 1)
  - August 21, 1973 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - September 18, 1973 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - September 26, 1973 Special Meeting (Box 1)
  - October 16, 1973 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - November 9, 1973 Special Meeting (Box 1)
  - November 26, 1973 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - December 18, 1973 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - January 22, 1974 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - February 19, 1974 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - March 9, 1974 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - April 16, 1974 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - May 21, 1974 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - June 3, 1974 Executive Meeting (Box 1)
  - June 25, 1974 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - June 28, 1974 Executive Meeting (Box 1)
  - July 16, 1974 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - August 5, 1974 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - September 17, 1974 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - October 10, 1974 Special Meeting (Box 1)
  - October 15, 1974 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - November 19, 1974 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - December 17, 1974 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - January 14, 1975 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - March 19, 1975 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - April 16, 1975 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - May 12, 1975 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - May 27, 1975 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - June 17, 1975 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - July 15, 1975 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - August 19, 1975 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - September 16, 1975 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - October 21, 1975 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - November 10, 1975 Executive Meeting (Box 1)
  - November 18, 1975 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - December 16, 1975 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - January 20, 1976 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - February 17, 1976 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - March 5, 1976 Executive Meeting (Box 1)
  - March 16, 1976 Regular Meeting (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Site Meetings (Box 1)
- Policy statements and other materials
  - Basic Policy Statements (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Policy/Program Information (Box 1)
  - Bulkley Log and personal miscellanea (Box 1)
  - Communications with Director 1975-1976 (Box 1)
- Organizational files
  - Annual reports (Box 2)
  - Budget:
    - Fiscal Year 1974 (Box 2)
    - Fiscal Year 1975 (Box 2)
    - Fiscal Year 1976 (Box 2)
    - Fiscal Year 1977 (Box 2)
  - Revenue Sharing Funds (Box 2)
  - Rotary Proposal (Box 2)
  - Dean Fund (Box 2)
  - 1973 Audit (Box 2)
  - 1975 Audit (HUD) (Box 2)
  - Management Study 1972 (Box 2)
  - Management Study 1975 (Box 2)
  - Maintenance Study 1975 (Box 2)
  - Personnel
    - 1974 (Box 2)
    - 1974 Director's Resignation (Box 2)
    - 1975 (Box 2)
    - 1976 (Box 2)
  - Project Change (Box 2)
  - Project Pride (Box 2)
  - Information about Miller Manor (Box 2)
  - Homeowners Project (Box 2)
  - Home Leasing Project (Box 2)
  - Public Housing Tenants Organization (Box 2)
  - Communication Line (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper clippings (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
  - Photographs: Exterior views of Miller Manor, senior citizen housing complex in Ann Arbor (Box 2)